<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>argument on</title><link>https://kris-brown.github.io/tags/argument/</link><description>Recent content in argument on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://kris-brown.github.io/tags/argument/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kant-Sellars thesis</title><link>https://kris-brown.github.io/Kant-Sellars-thesis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kris-brown.github.io/Kant-Sellars-thesis/</guid><description>From three premises:
what you need to move from Labeling to describing is situation in a space of implications space of implications must draw lines between implications that will between counterfactual circumstances under which the implication would still be good, and those in which wouldn&amp;rsquo;t the expressive job, not in the first instance, a descriptive job that&amp;rsquo;s characteristic of modal vocabulary is to make explicit those range those implications and those ranges of counterfactual robustness Put another way, suppose Sellars is right that modal expressions function as inference licenses.</description></item><item><title>Myth of the Given</title><link>https://kris-brown.github.io/Myth-of-the-Given/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kris-brown.github.io/Myth-of-the-Given/</guid><description>Author
A (semantic) holist argument against meaning-givenness, like Quines&amp;rsquo; Myth of the Museum against sense-givenness.
It is common to think that knowledge begins with experience - that there are particular experiences (raw sense data) that are privileged as certain, leading to a desire to cache out all semantic interpretations of other thoughts in terms of these certain experiences (otherwise they are nonsense).</description></item><item><title>Representation is socially determined</title><link>https://kris-brown.github.io/Representation-is-socially-determined/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kris-brown.github.io/Representation-is-socially-determined/</guid><description>Premises:
All normative relations are matters of functional roles in social practices Representation is normative Conclusion:
Representational relations are relations of social practice</description></item></channel></rss>